  export const filme = [
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20not%20the%20name%20of%20a%20%22Bond%20Girl%22%3F%20",
      correct_answer: "Vanessa%20Kensington",
      incorrect_answers: ["Pam%20Bouvier", "Mary%20Goodnight", "Wai%20Lin"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20movie%20released%20in%202016%20features%20Superman%20and%20Batman%20fighting%3F",
      correct_answer: "Batman%20v%20Superman%3A%20Dawn%20of%20Justice",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Batman%20v%20Superman%3A%20Superapocalypse",
        "Batman%20v%20Superman%3A%20Black%20of%20Knight",
        "Batman%20v%20Superman%3A%20Knightfall",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Daniel%20Radcliffe%20became%20a%20global%20star%20in%20the%20film%20industry%20due%20to%20his%20performance%20in%20which%20film%20franchise%3F",
      correct_answer: "Harry%20Potter",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Ted",
        "Spy%20Kids",
        "Pirates%20of%20the%20Caribbean%20",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Who%20directed%20%22E.T.%20the%20Extra-Terrestrial%22%20%281982%29%3F",
      correct_answer: "Steven%20Spielberg",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Stanley%20Kubrick",
        "James%20Cameron",
        "Tim%20Burton",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20is%20the%20highest%20grossing%20film%20of%20all%20time%20%28without%20adjusting%20for%20inflation%29%3F",
      correct_answer: "Avengers%3A%20Endgame",
      incorrect_answers: ["Jurassic%20World", "Avatar", "Titanic"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20animated%20movie%20was%20first%20to%20feature%20a%20celebrity%20as%20a%20voice%20actor%3F",
      correct_answer: "Aladdin",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Toy%20Story",
        "James%20and%20the%20Giant%20Peach",
        "The%20Hunchback%20of%20Notre%20Dame",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Who%20wrote%20and%20directed%20the%201986%20film%20%27Platoon%27%3F",
      correct_answer: "Oliver%20Stone",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Francis%20Ford%20Coppola",
        "Stanley%20Kubrick",
        "Michael%20Cimino",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Who%20played%20Deputy%20Marshal%20Samuel%20Gerard%20in%20the%201993%20film%20%22The%20Fugitive%22%3F",
      correct_answer: "Tommy%20Lee%20Jones",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Harrison%20Ford",
        "Harvey%20Keitel",
        "Martin%20Landau",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20movie%20contains%20the%20quote%2C%20%22Say%20hello%20to%20my%20little%20friend%21%22%3F",
      correct_answer: "Scarface",
      incorrect_answers: ["Reservoir%20Dogs", "Heat", "Goodfellas"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "Who%20directed%20the%202015%20movie%20%22The%20Revenant%22%3F",
      correct_answer: "Alejandro%20G.%20I%C3%B1%C3%A1rritu",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Christopher%20Nolan",
        "David%20Fincher",
        "Wes%20Anderson",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "The%20Queen%20song%20%60A%20Kind%20Of%20Magic%60%20is%20featured%20in%20which%201986%20film%3F",
      correct_answer: "Highlander",
      incorrect_answers: ["Flash%20Gordon", "Labyrinth", "Howard%20the%20Duck"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20was%20Dorothy%27s%20surname%20in%20%27The%20Wizard%20Of%20Oz%27%3F",
      correct_answer: "Gale",
      incorrect_answers: ["Perkins", "Day", "Parker"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20was%20the%20title%20of%20the%20first%20Bond%20movie%2C%20released%20in%201962%3F",
      correct_answer: "Dr.%20No",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "From%20Russia%20with%20Love",
        "Goldfinger",
        "Thunderball",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "This%20movie%20contains%20the%20quote%2C%20%22Houston%2C%20we%20have%20a%20problem.%22",
      correct_answer: "Apollo%2013",
      incorrect_answers: ["The%20Right%20Stuff", "Capricorn%20One", "Marooned"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "This%20movie%20contains%20the%20quote%2C%20%22I%20feel%20the%20need%20...%20the%20need%20for%20speed%21%22",
      correct_answer: "Top%20Gun",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Days%20of%20Thunder",
        "The%20Color%20of%20Money",
        "Cocktail",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "What%20was%20the%20first%20James%20Bond%20film%3F",
      correct_answer: "Dr.%20No",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Goldfinger",
        "From%20Russia%20With%20Love",
        "Thunderball",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20of%20these%20actors%2Factresses%20is%20NOT%20a%20part%20of%20the%20cast%20for%20the%202016%20movie%20%22Suicide%20Squad%22%3F",
      correct_answer: "Scarlett%20Johansson",
      incorrect_answers: ["Jared%20Leto", "Will%20Smith", "Margot%20Robbie"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20of%20these%20movies%20did%20Jeff%20Bridges%20not%20star%20in%3F",
      correct_answer: "The%20Hateful%20Eight",
      incorrect_answers: ["Tron%3A%20Legacy", "The%20Giver", "True%20Grit"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20movie%20includes%20a%20giant%20bunny-like%20spirit%20who%20has%20magic%20powers%20including%20growing%20trees%3F",
      correct_answer: "My%20Neighbor%20Totoro",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Hop",
        "Rise%20of%20the%20Guardians",
        "Alice%20in%20Wonderland",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "Who%20plays%20Alice%20in%20the%20Resident%20Evil%20movies%3F",
      correct_answer: "Milla%20Jovovich",
      incorrect_answers: ["Madison%20Derpe", "Milla%20Johnson", "Kim%20Demp"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Who%20is%20the%20main%20protagonist%20in%2C%20the%201985%20film%2C%20Back%20to%20the%20Future%3F",
      correct_answer: "Marty%20McFly",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Emmett%20%22Doc%22%20Brown",
        "Biff%20Tannen",
        "George%20McFly",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "In%20the%20movie%20%22Cast%20Away%22%20the%20main%20protagonist%27s%20best%20friend%20while%20on%20the%20island%20is%20named",
      correct_answer: "Wilson",
      incorrect_answers: ["Carson", "Jackson", "Willy"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Who%20in%20Pulp%20Fiction%20says%20%22No%2C%20they%20got%20the%20metric%20system%20there%2C%20they%20wouldn%27t%20know%20what%20the%20fuck%20a%20Quarter%20Pounder%20is.%22",
      correct_answer: "Vincent%20Vega",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Jules%20Winnfield",
        "Jimmie%20Dimmick",
        "Butch%20Coolidge",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "In%20%22Jurassic%20World%22%2C%20what%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20dinosaur%20that%20is%20a%20genetic%20hybrid%3F",
      correct_answer: "Indominus%20Rex",
      incorrect_answers: ["Mosasaurus", "Pteranodon", "Tyrannosaurus%20Rex%20"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20actor%20plays%20Obi-Wan%20Kenobi%20in%20Star%20Wars%20Episodes%20I-lll%3F",
      correct_answer: "Ewan%20McGregor",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Alec%20Guinness",
        "Hayden%20Christensen",
        "Liam%20Neeson",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "The%202002%20film%20%2228%20Days%20Later%22%20is%20mainly%20set%20in%20which%20European%20country%3F",
      correct_answer: "United%20Kingdom",
      incorrect_answers: ["France", "Italy", "Germany"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "In%20the%20movie%20%22Spaceballs%22%2C%20what%20are%20the%20Spaceballs%20attempting%20to%20steal%20from%20Planet%20Druidia%3F",
      correct_answer: "Air",
      incorrect_answers: ["The%20Schwartz", "Princess%20Lonestar", "Meatballs"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20was%20the%20first%20monster%20to%20appear%20alongside%20Godzilla%3F",
      correct_answer: "Anguirus",
      incorrect_answers: ["King%20Kong", "Mothra", "King%20Ghidora"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "In%20the%20movie%20Gremlins%2C%20after%20what%20time%20of%20day%20should%20you%20not%20feed%20Mogwai%3F",
      correct_answer: "Midnight",
      incorrect_answers: ["Evening", "Morning", "Afternoon"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "%22The%20first%20rule%20is%3A%20you%20don%27t%20talk%20about%20it%22%20is%20a%20reference%20to%20which%20movie%3F",
      correct_answer: "Fight%20Club",
      incorrect_answers: ["The%20Island", "Unthinkable", "American%20Pie"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "In%20the%202012%20film%2C%20%22The%20Lorax%22%2C%20who%20is%20the%20antagonist%3F",
      correct_answer: "Aloysius%20O%27Hare",
      incorrect_answers: ["Ted%20Wiggins", "The%20Once-Ler", "Grammy%20Norma"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "In%20the%201992%20film%20%22Army%20of%20Darkness%22%2C%20what%20name%20does%20Ash%20give%20to%20his%20double-barreled%20shotgun%3F",
      correct_answer: "Boomstick",
      incorrect_answers: ["Bloomstick", "Blastbranch", "2-Pump%20Chump"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "At%20the%20end%20of%20the%202001%20film%20%22Rat%20Race%22%2C%20whose%20concert%20do%20the%20contestants%20crash%3F",
      correct_answer: "Smash%20Mouth",
      incorrect_answers: ["Bowling%20for%20Soup", "Sum%2041", "Linkin%20Park"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Who%20plays%20the%20character%20of%20Po%20in%20the%20Kung%20Fu%20Panda%20movies%3F",
      correct_answer: "Jack%20Black",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Mirana%20Jonnes",
        "McConahey%20Ramses",
        "Jim%20Petersson",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "In%20the%20movie%20%22Blade%20Runner%22%2C%20what%20is%20the%20term%20used%20for%20human-like%20androids%20%3F",
      correct_answer: "Replicants",
      incorrect_answers: ["Cylons", "Synthetics", "Skinjobs"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "The%202016%20Disney%20animated%20film%20%27Moana%27%20is%20based%20on%20which%20culture%3F",
      correct_answer: "Polynesian",
      incorrect_answers: ["Native%20American", "Japanese", "Nordic"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "In%20the%201995%20film%20%22Balto%22%2C%20who%20are%20Steele%27s%20accomplices%3F",
      correct_answer: "Kaltag%2C%20Nikki%2C%20and%20Star",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Dusty%2C%20Kirby%2C%20and%20Ralph",
        "Nuk%2C%20Yak%2C%20and%20Sumac",
        "Jenna%2C%20Sylvie%2C%20and%20Dixie",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20island%20that%20%22Jurassic%20Park%22%20is%20built%20on%3F",
      correct_answer: "Isla%20Nublar",
      incorrect_answers: ["Isla%20Sorna", "Isla%20Muerta", "Isla%20Pena"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20was%20Bruce%20Campbell%27s%20iconic%20one-liner%20after%20getting%20a%20chainsaw%20hand%20in%20Evil%20Dead%202%3F",
      correct_answer: "Groovy.",
      incorrect_answers: ["Gnarly.", "Perfect.", "Nice."],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "For%20the%20film%20%22Raiders%20of%20The%20Lost%20Ark%22%2C%20what%20was%20Harrison%20Ford%20sick%20with%20during%20the%20filming%20of%20the%20Cairo%20chase%3F",
      correct_answer: "Dysentery",
      incorrect_answers: ["Anemia", "Constipation", "Acid%20Reflux%20"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "In%20which%20film%20does%20Humphrey%20Bogart%20say%20the%20famous%20line%2C%20%22Here%27s%20looking%20at%20you%2C%20kid%22%3F",
      correct_answer: "Casablanca",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "The%20Maltese%20Falcon",
        "The%20Treasure%20of%20the%20Sierra%20Madre",
        "Citizen%20Kane",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20of%20these%20Movies%20was%20NOT%20released%20in%201996%3F",
      correct_answer: "Gladiator",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Independence%20Day",
        "The%20Rock",
        "Mission%3A%20Impossible",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20fictional%20retro-mod%20band%20starring%20Austin%20Powers%20as%20the%20lead%20vocalist%3F",
      correct_answer: "Ming%20Tea",
      incorrect_answers: ["Cough%20Fi", "Spear%20Mint", "Mister%20E"],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "Who%20directed%20the%20Kill%20Bill%20movies%3F",
      correct_answer: "Quentin%20Tarantino",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Arnold%20Schwarzenegger",
        "David%20Lean",
        "Stanley%20Kubrick",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "In%20%22ALF%22%2C%20what%20was%20ALF%27s%20real%20name%3F",
      correct_answer: "Gordon%20Shumway",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Gordon%20Milipp",
        "Gordon%20Foster",
        "Gordon%20von%20Gam",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20of%20the%20following%20actors%20has%20only%20been%20in%20a%20Quentin%20Tarantino%20directed%20film%20once%3F",
      correct_answer: "John%20Travolta",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Christoph%20Waltz",
        "Harvey%20Keitel",
        "Samuel%20L.%20Jackson",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20historical%20time%20period%20was%20the%20center%20of%20the%20Assassin%E2%80%99s%20Creed%20movie%20%282016%29%3F",
      correct_answer: "Spanish%20Inquisition",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Victorian%20England",
        "French%20Revolution",
        "Colonial%20America",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Who%20plays%20Jack%20Burton%20in%20the%20movie%20%22Big%20Trouble%20in%20Little%20China%3F%22",
      correct_answer: "Kurt%20Russell",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Patrick%20Swayze",
        "John%20Cusack",
        "Harrison%20Ford",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "In%20the%20movie%20%22V%20for%20Vendetta%2C%22%20what%20is%20the%20date%20that%20masked%20vigilante%20%22V%22%20urges%20people%20to%20remember%3F",
      correct_answer: "November%205th",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "November%206th",
        "November%204th",
        "September%205th",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "The%201996%20film%20%27Fargo%27%20is%20primarily%20set%20in%20which%20US%20state%3F",
      correct_answer: "Minnesota",
      incorrect_answers: ["North%20Dakota", "South%20Dakota", "Wisconsin"],
    },
  ];